unfpa.org 2004-12-28

# UNFPA: HELP: Terms and Conditions of Use

Privacy Policy

If you are just browsing on the UNFPA's web site (www.unfpa.org), we do not collect any personal information regarding your use of the site. However, if you register for an email newsletter, or make a donation on-line, you will be asked for personal information, such as your name and email address. 

Certain information about the user, such as IP addresses, navigation through site, software used, time spent and other similar information, may be stored on UNFPA servers in small data pieces known as "cookies," which may also be written to the User's computer system. These cookies will not specifically identify the User. The information will be used internally only for web site traffic analysis. If the User specifically provides unique identifying information, such as name, address and other information on forms stored on this site, such information will only be used for statistical purposes and will not be published for general access. UNFPA, however, assumes no responsibility for the security of this information. 

In addition, UNFPA also records your IP address, which is the Internet address of your computer, and information such as your browser type and operating system. This information helps us learn about the geographical distribution of our website visitors and the technology they use to access our site. This information is never connected with the personal information you supply to us if you register on our website. 

Registering on our site is optional. If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use the UNFPA's web site. However, you will not be able to receive email newsletters. 

If you register for a newsletter, forum, consultation, or conference UNFPA will not share, sell, distribute or rent your information to anyone. If you enter into a transaction on our Publications web site, your information will not be shared.

UNFPA employs a range of technologies to protect the information maintained on our systems from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Back to top
